# Olorunda Kehinde Olusola

CONTACT

1b Abayomi Shonuga Crescent Lekki Phase 1 Lagos kehindeolorunda@gmail.com +234 (80) 698 16405

#### PROFILE SUMMARY

Social Media Analyst who is able to expertly mingle the various platforms to work together. Adept at Internet technology computer productivity software and developing effective Internet marketing programs. Specializes in emerging social media platforms, human psychology and SEO marketing tactics.

## CAREER OBJECTIVE

- To share ideas, build plans and work tirelessly and cooperatively hence increasing productivity and self development, thereby making organizational dreams real.
- To positively use my diverse skills, knowledge, interest and ability to work in an enterprising and veritable organization through training, innovations, initiatives and dedication as well as to pursue organizational goals.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Cab Management Company, Victoria Island, Oct 2016 — Present

Lagos

Customer Relation Officer

Freelance Project Writer 2014 — Present

Social Media analyst/ Content Writer

Federal Government College, Nise, Oct 2015 — Sept 2016

Anambra State

Assistant English Instructor

Awelewa Commercial Bureau Aug 2009 — Sept 2010

**Business Administrator** 

# **EDUCATION**

English and International Relations Sept 2010 — Sept 2014

Osun State University, Oshogbo

Courses include: International Trade, Human Management, Researching, Diplomacy, Creative Writing, Communication Skills and Arts

# **QUALIFICATIONS**

B.A (Hons) English and International Relations (Second Class Upper Division)

#### PROFESSIONAL COMPETENCIES

Passion for social media and internet marketing industries.

Olorunda Kehinde Olusola

- Outstanding ability to think creatively, and identify and resolve problems.
- Attention to detail and the ability to effectively multi-task in a deadline driven atmosphere.
- Ability to clearly and effectively articulate thoughts and points.
- High levels of integrity, autonomy, and self-motivation.
- Excellent analytical, organizational, project management and time management skills.

#### **INTEREST**

- Keeping pace with social media and internet marketing industry trends and developments.
- Managing and helping in the creation of marketing content to socialize and use for social media purposes.
- Monitoring and evaluating social media results.
- Building and nurturing social media platform- specific communities and audiences.
- Interested in supporting SEO goals

## EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Reading and freelance writing Researching Social Media marketing

## OTHER INFORMATION

Google student club member 2013 - 2015
Certified as an online basic & professional by Google Web Academy.
Served as Chief Whip English Studies Students' Association (ENSSA) 2011/2012
Served as Vice President (Student Union Government, Osun State University, Ikire Campus) 2012/2013
Member of UNIOSUN Ikire Campus Press 2011 - 2013

## **REFERENCES**

Available on request.

Olorunda Kehinde Olusola